http://www.airforcemuseum.co.nz/privacy/

Privacy Policy
The Internet offers the chance to collect information about site users. This information can be personally identifiable information or aggregated information. However your privacy is important to us and we want to be sure that you understand the terms and conditions relating to the way in which we collect information and the use of that information.
This Privacy Policy tells you what information we collect, what we do with it and your rights to view, correct or change it.
The information we collect
The Air Force Museum of New Zealand operates the website www.airforcemuseum.co.nz. As part of our operations we may gather certain types of information about the users of our sites:
Personally Identifiable Information
This is provided by you when you register for services that we may offer.
Examples of these services include:
Signing up to our email database
Registering for Museum events (e.g. Open Cockpit event)
Entering competitions
Purchasing from our online shop
Making a Holiday Programme booking (note that this booking form is managed by Friendly Manager, a third party booking software which is not hosted on the Air Force Museum of New Zealand website)
Using our 'How to donate an item' form
Using our web contact forms to contact us.
Providing this information will always be optional for you. However, some services may not be available to you if you choose not to provide it.
Aggregated Data
This information is generated by our systems as they track traffic through our sites. This information does not identify you personally and is not linked to the personally identifiable information that you may have provided.
Who we share this information with
The information is be hosted with our service provider.
Our agreements with them protect the information that we collect from any unauthorised use.
The aggregated data (not the personally identifiable information) may be shared with third parties such as advertisers or business partners.
Your personally identifiable information will only be shared with third parties when we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law.
Only if your prior permission has been obtained would we share the information with specified third parties.
What else we do with personally identifiable information
We have collected this information in order to provide the best possible service to you while you are visiting our site. To this end we may use the information that you provide for the following purposes:
To verify your identity if you need help with a forgotten password or you are having login problems with one of our site services.
To process any transactions that you might make on our site.
To help provide any other services that you have requested.
To offer the most relevant information suitable to you and your interests.
For any marketing, promotional, publicity, marketing or market research that we might undertake.
For any other purposes for which you have given permission.
What about cookies?
A cookie is a small file that resides on your computer and is recognised by our server when you visit our site. A cookie does not provide us with any personally identifiable information. It does provide details of your IP address, the computer platform that you use (e.g. Mac or Windows), the browser that you use (eg Microsoft Explorer or Netscape) and what domain you are accessing our sites from.
With this information we can do the following:
Track traffic patterns to our site.
Ensure that the most relevant content is being shown.
Allow you to enter certain site member services without having to log in each time you visit.
If you would rather we did not use cookies with you, you can refuse them by turning them off in your browser and/or deleting them from your hard drive. You will still be able to visit our site.
What about our business partners?
This Privacy Policy only relates to our sites. You should be aware that we are not responsible for the practices of business partners or sites we may link to. You should check their privacy policies before providing personally identifiable information to them or any other third party.
Opting in and opting out
You will always have the option to opt in to certain services and to opt out of those services at any stage. This means you may change your mind at any stage about participating in any of our member services.
Your right to access your information
The Privacy Act of 1993 gives you the right to access and correct your personal information. To find out more about how to do this, please contact us. Alternatively, post your corrections to the attention of the Communications Manager at Air Force Museum, Private Bag 4739, Christchurch 8140.
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
Open daily from 10am to 4pm (except Christmas Day)
Entry to the Museum is free, donations are appreciated.
45 Harvard Ave, Wigram, Christchurch | 03 343 9532
Contact Us  |  Get Directions  |  Donate  |  Sign up
We welcome visitors of all abilities
PRIVACY  |  TERMS  © Air Force Museum of New Zealand 2020.
BlogContactShopVISIT
Plan Your VisitGroup VisitsVisitor Services & AccessibilityShop Back
WHAT’S ON
What to See
ExhibitionsDisplaysGalleries Back
What to Do
Behind the Scenes TourMosquito Mission Flight SimulatorMuseum HuntsHands-on ExperiencesDiscover Historic WigramGroup ActivitiesHoliday ProgrammesBirthday Parties Back
Back
COLLECTIONS & RESEARCH
ConserveResearchDonate an Item Back
LEARN
Early ChildhoodPrimary EducationSecondary EducationESOL GroupsPlan your group visitWhat We Can Offer Back
JOIN & SUPPORT
About our MuseumMake a DonationOur TeamJoin Our Team Back
VENUE HIRE
Thérèse Angelo WingAircraft HallAtriumBrevet LoungeDonaldson RoomMorrison RoomTheatre Back
